<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Reviews on Ateli-weird</title>
    <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Reviews on Ateli-weird</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 13:46:59 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Provenance</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/provenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 13:46:59 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/provenance/</guid>
      <description>Set in the same universe as the Imperial Radch trilogy, this book follows Ingray, a young woman from the Hwean system. When a purchase goes wrong, she has to juggle with her politics and family to prevent disaster.
After the original trilogy, it was nice to see what the Radchaai look like from outside of their domain. It also contrasted nicely with Breq&amp;rsquo;s perspective from the previous books - the conflict is a smaller scale, and though Hwae is seemingly unrelated to the goings-on of the Radchaai, I still found myself invested in Ingray&amp;rsquo;s struggle by the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ancillary Justice (and sequels)</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/ancillary-justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:49:53 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/ancillary-justice/</guid>
      <description>Ancillary Justice
The first in a loose trilogy, Breq is the lone remaining body of a ship&amp;rsquo;s AI following a disaster not specified - what we know is she&amp;rsquo;s angry, and she&amp;rsquo;s seeking someone.
I found Breq&amp;rsquo;s perspective interesting; the use of a single pronoun in a society where gender isn&amp;rsquo;t baked into the language was fresh to read, and executed fairly cleanly. I&amp;rsquo;m sure essays could (and probably have) be written on that alone, but what I found far more intriguing was the perspective of a hive-mind AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Eternal Sky Trilogy</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-eternal-sky-trilogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 11:40:05 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-eternal-sky-trilogy/</guid>
      <description>The Eternal Sky trilogy follows the journey of Re Temur, as he seeks to reclaim his grandfather&amp;rsquo;s throne. Along with Temur, the series follows a number of other character perspectives.
As with the sequel series, Bear does a brilliant job of handling this; despite the large cast of characters most of them feel well fleshed out and interesting. These novels felt quite dense at times though - though I never struggled to get through them, they each took a long time to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vorkosigan Saga</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-vorkosigan-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:22:57 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-vorkosigan-saga/</guid>
      <description>Overall, I enjoyed this series, with some major caveats.
Miles is a very fun character to follow, and these books hold up well. The early books are (mostly) very fun, and I found most of them no challenge to get through.
My main problem was with the latter half of the series. As with most of Bujold&amp;rsquo;s books, there&amp;rsquo;s a tendency for characters to get happily traditionally married by the end of the series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Theory of Haunting</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/a-theory-of-haunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:19:19 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/a-theory-of-haunting/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll admit, I&amp;rsquo;m biased towards Monette&amp;rsquo;s writing. I read Melusine a lot back in highschool, and it was a keystone in forming my tastes.
I enjoyed the mystery of this book. Kyle Murchison Booth is always fun to read, and Monette is very good at what she does. I only wish it was a little longer, as the ending felt quite abrupt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Locked Tomb</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-locked-tomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:15:49 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-locked-tomb/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed these books, and it&amp;rsquo;s always fun to see a NZ author. All the characters are interesting and each of the books have a central mystery that is both intriguing to find out and devastating at the conclusion.
Unfortunately, something about the writing stopped me from clicking with the characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Murderbot Diaries</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/murderbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:10:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/murderbot/</guid>
      <description>Books 1-6
The Murderbot Diaries is a series of novels and novellas following Murderbot, a sentient bot who has hacked its governor chip.
I loved this series. Most of the novellas are relatively short, and easy reading. Despite that, each one manages a good amount of depth in terms of character, and Murderbot&amp;rsquo;s point of view is distinctive and fun to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Witch King</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/witch-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 18:17:36 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/witch-king/</guid>
      <description>Witch King follows the story of the demon Kai, who awakens after being killed, and his journey to find out what happened.
I wanted to enjoy Witch King more than I did. I loved Kai as a protagonist, and Wells&amp;rsquo; writing was enjoyable, but it suffered from the split timeline.
Witch King has two timelines - one set in the present, and one in the past. Both were very interesting, but I felt like not enough time was spent on either, leaving us with two half-stories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>