<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>queer on Ateli-weird</title>
    <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/tags/queer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in queer on Ateli-weird</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:19:19 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rhenn.neocities.org/tags/queer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Theory of Haunting</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/a-theory-of-haunting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:19:19 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/a-theory-of-haunting/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll admit, I&amp;rsquo;m biased towards Monette&amp;rsquo;s writing. I read Melusine a lot back in highschool, and it was a keystone in forming my tastes.
I enjoyed the mystery of this book. Kyle Murchison Booth is always fun to read, and Monette is very good at what she does. I only wish it was a little longer, as the ending felt quite abrupt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Locked Tomb</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-locked-tomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 20:15:49 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/the-locked-tomb/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed these books, and it&amp;rsquo;s always fun to see a NZ author. All the characters are interesting and each of the books have a central mystery that is both intriguing to find out and devastating at the conclusion.
Unfortunately, something about the writing stopped me from clicking with the characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Witch King</title>
      <link>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/witch-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 18:17:36 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rhenn.neocities.org/reviews/witch-king/</guid>
      <description>Witch King follows the story of the demon Kai, who awakens after being killed, and his journey to find out what happened.
I wanted to enjoy Witch King more than I did. I loved Kai as a protagonist, and Wells&amp;rsquo; writing was enjoyable, but it suffered from the split timeline.
Witch King has two timelines - one set in the present, and one in the past. Both were very interesting, but I felt like not enough time was spent on either, leaving us with two half-stories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>